Carmen McRae Collection of Musical Arrangements and Other Materials
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1931-1976 (Box 1-40)
  - San Francisco, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #249 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Santa was here, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Satin Doll, Duke Ellington / Billy Strayhorn / Johnny Mercer; Drum part; Small group #196 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Say cheese, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Say hello for me, John Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Sea journey, Chick Corea / Neville Potter; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Sea mist, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Searching for true love, Mary Lou Williams / Gracie Glassman; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Season in the Sun, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Second chance, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #253 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - See me now, Parts (guitar, double bass); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #285 (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Separate ways, Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/25)
  - The shadow of your smile, Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #329 (Box-folder 18/26)
  - She doesn't know (I love her), Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Sheet music with annotations, Published sheet music; Titles: Afterthoughts; Any old time; Famous song hits, no.2; Gloomy Sunday; How little we know; Michel Legrand songs; Over the rainbow; Remind me; Send in the clowns; Sorry seems to be the hardest word; The sound of silence; A star is born; Whoever you are, I love you; Yesterday, when I was young; You're blasé (Box-folder 18/28)
  - She's gone, Chuck Mangione / Bat McGrath; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/29)
  - A shoulder to cry on, Parts (alto saxophone, piano, drums, strings); Small group #155 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Signing off, Leonard Feather / Jessyca Russell; Lead sheet (Box-folder 18/31)
  - Silent Spring, Allan Paul Shatkin; Guitar part (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Simple life, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #16 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - Simple song and A new song, Leonard Bernstein / Stephen Schwartz; Lead sheet; From Leonard Bernstein's "Mass" (Box-folder 18/34)
  - Simple thing, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins (Box-folder 18/35)
  - Skating in Central Park, John Lewis / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 18/36)
  - Sky, Piano part; Small group #48 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Skylark, Hoagy Carmichael / Johnny Mercer; Piano/conductor part; Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Skyliner, Charlie Barnet aka Dale Bennett; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #48 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - A sleepin' bee, Harold Arlen; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins; Small group #90 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Smiling phases, Steve Winwood / James Capaldi / Chris Wood; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/4)
  - So easy to forget, Jean Galvis / Caryl Young; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/5)
  - So easy - without you, Stacey Dietz; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/6)
  - So long, Score and parts (piano, double bass, drums, strings) (parts incomplete); Arranged by Marty Paich; Small group #289 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - So what's new, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Jimmy Jones; Small group #385 (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Soft, Chuck Mangione; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Some other Spring, Irene Kitchings / Arthur Herzog Jr.; Guitar part; Small group #41 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Some time ago, Chick Corea / Neville Potter; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Something, George Harrison; Score and parts (horn, woodwind, cymbalum, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Arif Mardin; Small group #381 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Something happens, Erroll Garner / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Something I dreamed last night, Herbert Magidson / Jack Yellen; Score and parts (production/conductor, English horn, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Frank Hunter; Small group #175 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Something to live for, Billy Strayhorn; Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #71 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Song for my father, Horace Silver / Jon Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/13)
  - A song for you, Parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, flute, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Gene DiNovi; Small group #419 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - The sound of silence, Guitar part (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Sounds of Spring, Leonard Feather / Benny Green; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/16)
  - Speak low, Kurt Weill; Score and parts (conductor, vocal, woodwinds 1-4, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Small group #11 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Spread to all, Oliver Nelson / Gail Fisher Levy; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Spring can really hang you up the most, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #245 (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Spring will never melt my heart this year, Bill Rubenstein / Carmen Huesman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 19/19)
  - Star eyes, Gene De Paul / Don Raye; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Star eyes, Gene De Paul / Don Raye; Parts (piano, double bass, drums, celesta); Arranged by Bill Holman; Small group #19 (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Stardust, Hoagy Carmichael; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, piano/conductor, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Stardust, Hoagy Carmichael; Piano part; Small group #99 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Straight, no chaser, Thelonious Monk / Sally Swisher (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Straighten up and fly right, Nat King Cole / Irving Mills; Lead sheet and piano/drum part (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Street of dreams, Rhythm lead sheet (Box-folder 20/5)
  - The Summer knows, Michel Legrand / Marilyn Bergman/ Alan Bergman; Score; sketch; Arranged by Tom Garvin (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Sunday, Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #152 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Sunday, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-3, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Franck Collett (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Sunday, Parts (piano/conductor, bassoon, celesta); Arranged by Bill Holman (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Sunny, Parts (vocal, trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Sunshine, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Sure I do, Gene DiNovi; Lead sheet; Laid in: note from DiNovi to McRae (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown, Ben Bernie / Maceo Pinkard / Kenneth Casey; Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, trombone 1-2, horn 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown, Ben Bernie / Maceo Pinkard / Kenneth Casey; Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown, Ben Bernie / Maceo Pinkard / Kenneth Casey; Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/guitar/conductor, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Sweet Georga Brown, Ben Bernie / Maceo Pinkard / Kenneth Casey; Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #168 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Sweet life, Tadd Dameron / Bernie Hanighen; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Sweet Lorraine, Lead sheet (sketch); Small group #211 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Sweet pumpkin, Blue Mitchell / Ronnell Bright; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #160 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Sweetest [chaser], Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, double bass, drums); Small group #211 (Box-folder 32/4)
  - The sweetest sounds, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #162 (Box-folder 20/16)
  - Sweetness and light, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Swing high, swing low, Carroll Coates; Lead sheet (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Take him, Master rhythm/lead sheet (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Take me (let me prove my love to you), Trudy Rhone / E. L. Howard; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Take me home, Johnny Mandel / Marilyn Bergman / Alan Bergman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Talk about cozy, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Talk about loving you, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Talk away, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Teach me tonight, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #89 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Tender touch, Jimmy Heath; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Tenderly, Walter Gross / Jack Lawrence; Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #5 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Thank you, Leonard Bernstein / Stephen Schwartz; Lead sheet; From Leonard Bernstein's "Mass" (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Thank you for your love, Carroll Coates; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Thanks for nothing, Johnny Rotella / Jerry Gladstone; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 21/12)
  - That old black magic, Harold Arlen; Piano part (Box-folder 21/13)
  - That ole devil called love, Allan Roberts / Doris Fisher / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet; On verso: lead sheet for "Dream of life" (Box-folder 21/14)
  - That reminds me, Parts (piano/guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #216 (Box-folder 21/15)
  - That's all, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 21/16)
  - That's for me, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins; Small group #102 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - That's what it's all about, Mildred Mayne; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/17)
  - Thelonious Monk, Parts (piano, guitar) (Box-folder 21/18)
  - Theme bows, String parts; Arranged by George A. Rhodes; At top: Sammy D. Jr. (Box-folder 21/19)
  - There are days when I don't think of you at all, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/20)
  - There I've said it again, Lead sheet (sketch) (Box-folder 21/21)
  - There will come a time, S. Brooks; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Tom Garvinn (Box-folder 37/3)
  - There'll be no tomorrow see Brubeck folder, Dave Brubeck; Lyric sheet
  - There'll be other times, Margaret Jones / Marian McPartland; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/22)
  - These foolish things, G. Pocock; Lyric sheet; Inscribed: New lyrics (Box-folder 21/23)
  - These times, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #349 (Box-folder 21/24)
  - They all laughed, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #18 (Box-folder 21/25)
  - [They] can't take that away from me, George Gershwin / Ira Gershwin; Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #52 (Box-folder 21/26)
  - They long to be close to you, Burt Bacharach / Hal David; Parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, woodwinds 1-5, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Gene DiNovi (Box-folder 21/27)
  - They long to be close to you, Burt Bacharach / Hal David; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 21/28)
  - This could be the start of something, Steve Allen; Score; Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 21/29)
  - This is all I ask, Lead sheet; Small group #263 (Box-folder 21/30)
  - This is love, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/31)
  - This little love of ours, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 21/32)
  - This year, Lead sheet; parts (B-flat horns, double bass); Small group #355 (Box-folder 21/33)
  - Thou swell, Piano part; Small group #56 (Box-folder 21/34)
  - Three little words, Bert Kalmar / Harry Ruby; Sheet music, score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #92 (Box-folder 32/5)
  - The thrill is gone, Score and parts (prod/conductor, vocal, oboe, flute, clarinet, bass clarinet, piano, guitar, strings) (missing double bass, drums); Arranged by Frank Hunter (Box-folder 21/35)
  - Thunderstruck, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/1)
  - 'Till you told me, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass); Small group #273 (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Time after time, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #56 (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Time for love, Leonard Feather; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Tip toe gently, Paulette Girard / Matt Matthews; Parts (piano, drums); Small group #10 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - 'Tis Autumn, Score; string parts; Arranged by Benny Carter for Francy Boland arrangement; Inscribed: Pearl Bailey Show (Box-folder 22/6)
  - To our friends, Stacey Dietz; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/7)
  - To thy self be true, Carroll Coates; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Tomorrow when I wake up, I'll be beautiful!, Dorothy Beagle Helle; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Too close for comfort, Double bass part; Small group #126 (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Too good, Score; lead sheet; parts (vocal, horn, harp, woodwinds 1-2, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz; strings arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #297 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Torchy, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/11)
  - Trance (when you look in my eyes), Carlos Quintana; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/12)
  - Travelin' blues see Brubeck folder, Dave Brubeck; Lyric sheet
  - Travelin' light, Dave Brubeck; Piano part; Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #136 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Tribute to Benny Carter, Bob Friedman; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Tricotism, Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/15)
  - The trouble with hello is goodbye, Dave Grusin / Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman; Parts (flugel 1-4, trombone 1-3, tenor saxophone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Frank Collett (Box-folder 22/16)
  - The trouble with hello is goodbye, Dave Grusin / Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman; Parts (vocal, trumpet 1-2, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone); Arranged by Bill Holman (Box-folder 22/17)
  - The trouble with hello is goodbye, Dave Grusin / Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman; Parts (vocal lead, choir, piano 1-2, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 22/18)
  - Try a little softer, Parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Try and stop me, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/20)
  - Two boys, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 22/21)
  - Two people (from two worlds apart), Billie Holiday / Jeanne Burns; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/22)
  - Unexpected days, Neville Potter / Stanley Clarke; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 22/23)
  - Unhappy, Jack Reardon / Marvin Fisher; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Unidentified fragments, Lead sheets and scores (Box-folder 22/25)
  - Unidentified lyric sheets (Box-folder 22/26)
  - Unlucky day, Ray Brown / Sy Lefco; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/27)
  - Until (I find another you), John Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 22/28)
  - Until it's time, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Until it's time, Score; Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Until it's time, Lead sheet and parts (guitar, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 22/29)
  - Until the real thing comes along, Sammy Cahn / Saul Chaplin / L.E. Freeman; Lead sheet (no lyrics) (Box-folder 22/30)
  - Until you smiled at me, Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman / Dave Grusin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/31)
  - Upside down [Flor de lis], Regina Werneck / Caetano Viana; Lead sheet; On verso: double bass part (Box-folder 22/32)
  - Use your head, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 22/33)
  - Van Lingle Mungo, Dave Frishberg; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/1)
  - The very thought of you, Parts (piano, double bass); Arranged by Belford Hendricks; Small group #213 (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Violets for your furs, Tom Adair / Matt Dennis; Lyric and lead sheet (Box-folder 23/3)
  - The visit (A visita), Ivan Lins, Victor Martins, Regina Werneck; Lead sheet and parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Wait for me, Charles DeForest; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Walkin', Richie Carpenter / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Walking happy, Sammy Cahn / Jimmy Van Heusen; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Oliver Nelson; Small group #210 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Waltz for a rainy be-bop evening, Richie Cole; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Wanting you, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #43 (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Watch what happens, Michel Legrand / Norman Gimbel; Parts (piano, drums); Small group #367 (Box-folder 23/10)
  - We should fall in love, William Weber; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/11)
  - Weak for the man, Parts (alto saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Small group #1533 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Weep no more, Dave Brubeck; Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #223 (Box-folder 23/13)
  - We'll be together again, Carl T. Fischer / Frankie Laine; Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #21 (Box-folder 23/14)
  - What am I going to do?, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/15)
  - What are you doing (the rest of your life), Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #413 (Box-folder 23/16)
  - What can I say [after I say I'm sorry], Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton (Box-folder 23/17)
  - What can I say after I say I'm sorry, Parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 23/18)
  - What can you do, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/19)
  - What cha gonna do?, Score and parts (horn, oboe 1-2, bassoon, piano/guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Arif Mardin; Small group # 395 (Box-folder 37/5)
  - What game shall we play today, Chick Corea / Neville Potter; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 23/20)
  - What has happened to Joe, Bobby Troup; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/31)
  - What is, Blossom Dearie / Mike Conner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/32)
  - What kind of fool am I?, Leslie Bricusse / Anthony Newley; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #247 (Box-folder 33/1)
  - What kind of fool [am I], Parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, double bass, drums); Arranged by Rocky Cole (Box-folder 23/33)
  - What you gonna do?, Score (trio) (Box-folder 23/34)
  - Whatever became of us, Carol Coleman / Julian Frazin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/35)
  - Whatever possessed me, Tad Dameron / Bernie Hanighan; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/26)
  - What's new, Bob Haggart; Parts (piano, double bass, drums, celesta, vibes, bells); Small group #159 (Box-folder 23/27)
  - What's the matter with me, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 23/28)
  - When I fall in love, Victor Young / Edward Heyman; Piano part; Small group #143 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - When I see you, Melba Joyce; Piano-vocal score; Arranged by Russ Turner (Box-folder 24/2)
  - When I was young, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #154 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - When laughs didn't cost a thing, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/4)
  - When she's (he's) in my arms, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/5)
  - When Summer turns to snow, Dave Grusin / Marilyn Bergman / Alan Bergman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/6)
  - [When] Sunny gets blue, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Double bass part; Small group #211 (Box-folder 24/7)
  - When the morning glories wake up in the morning, Traditional; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/8)
  - When the newness wears off, Bobby Laurel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/9)
  - When red red robin goes bob bob bobbin' along, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, tenor saxophone, clarinet, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 33/2)
  - When the swallows come back to Capistrano, Leon T. Rene; Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn 1-4, tenor saxophone, clarinet, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 33/3)
  - When will it end (Theme from the movie P.J.), Neal Hefti / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/10)
  - When you get around to me, Richard Ahlert; Lead sheet and parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #365 (Box-folder 24/11)
  - When your lover has gone, Einar Aaron Swan; Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #219 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - When you're away, Victor Herbert / Henry Blossom; Score (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Where?, Randy Weston / John Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/13)
  - Where are the words, F. Servino; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/14)
  - Where did it go?, Score and parts (vocal, trombone 1-4, horn 1-2, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz; Small group #301 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - Where to from here (Ballad of the divorced), Bobby Laurel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/15)
  - Where were you when I needed you, Lead sheet (chords) and drum part (Box-folder 24/16)
  - Where would you be, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #184 (Box-folder 24/17)
  - Whispser not, Benny Golson / Leonard Feather; Lead sheet and parts (tenor saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #146 (Box-folder 24/18)
  - Who, baby, Dorothy Beagle Helle; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/19)
  - Who can I turn to, Leslie Bricusse / Anthony Newley; Score and parts (horn 1-4, oboe, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #315 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Who gave me the power, Christine Gardner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/20)
  - Who gave you permission, Billy Goldenberg / Marilyn Bergman / Alan Bergman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/21)
  - Who were you, G. Palao / Mary O' Brien; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/22)
  - Why did it have to be someone like you, Patricia Petremont; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 24/23)
  - Why did you put me down, Mildred Mayne; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/24)
  - Why I let you go, Oscar Castro-Neves / Gene Lees; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 24/25)
  - Wild one, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/26)
  - Will love come along again, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/27)
  - Willo the wisp, Ronnell Bright / Paul F. Webster; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/28)
  - Wind in the willow, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 24/29)
  - Winter in May, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn, woodwinds 1-2, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Wish I were, Guitar / rhythm section part; Small group #166 (Box-folder 24/30)
  - With feeling, Marvin Fisher / Bart Howard; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 24/31)